What?!
Oden, you're leaving?!
There'll be less trouble, but we'll miss him.
I hear a monster lives in Kuri.
A demon by the name of Ashura Doji.
Kuri is a cancer in Wano...
Even Shogun Sukiyaki cannot control it.
The authorities are powerless to apprehend
criminals who take refuge in Kuri.
But they will die there anyway
if their strength is lacking.
Such a lawless region might
as well be another country!
Fascinating! I shall tour the land Wano!
Take care!
Kin! Denjiro!
Come visit us again!
See you!
He comes and goes as he pleases.
He is a free spirit.
Lord Yasuie!
We have a problem!
Look at the state of his accommodations!
What kind of lifestyle would cause this?!
We must charge him for the repairs!
Or we just pretend we were
struck by a natural disaster...
My lord, you are too soft on him!
Lord Yasuie!
What now?
There is money missing?
Yes, and I am certain
it was locked in the safe!
Um...
It pains me to say this...
but I witnessed the whole thing!
Um... Lord Oden...
tucked the money into
his inner breast pocket...
I knew he did it!
He bit the hands that fed him!
This is unforgivable!
I think Oden would have taken it openly.
Are you sure, Orochi?
Y-Yes! My apologies!
I was so scared that I couldn't stop him!
After leaving Hakumai, Oden's group continued
to cause trouble throughout Wano
as they headed toward Kuri.
How long are you two going to follow me?!
Forever!
We love you so much!
– He looks annoyed!
Hey! Why are you standing out there?
As your retainers, we must stand guard.
Come in, you idiots!
– Oden!
What are you doing?
I'm keeping a logbook.
Apparently, voyagers overseas write
in them every day on their ships.
The following are Oden's own
words regarding his journeys.
In Ringo, we came across
a couple of starving brothers in rags.
Get lost!
They were trying to earn money
by dancing, but people were cold.
Why are you two following me?!
Stop eating, you brats!
I want more.
I said stop!
Do not give him any more!
They mentioned being
the heirs to a school of dance,
but their father was arrested,
breaking up their family.
They brazenly ate our oden,
sobbing all the while.
In Kibi, there was a ghoul who
collected hair from the living and dead alike.
He was a freak who made a living
selling brushes made from the hair.
Whoa! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I thought you were a corpse!
I punched him for coming after my hair,
but then he began to follow me too.
He claimed to have suffered—
and deservedly so—from persecution.
In the forest-covered Udon, there were
rumors of a notorious mountain bandit.
They said women would be abducted,
and men would be beaten soundly.
Why are you all following me?!
You're telling me!
Is that the mountain bandit?!
Jump!
Lord Oden!
The prodigious ninja, Raizo, quit the Kozuki Clan's
Oniwabanshu after a kunoichi broke his heart.
I cannot live my life in hiding any longer!
He looks annoyed...
Kozuki Oden has come to Kuri?
He's the shogun's son!
I wanna kill him myself!
Catch him and bring him here!
– Yes, sir!
Those in power... We hate them most of all!
Where's Oden?
He went south of here to take a dump.
Wasn't that yesterday?
He sometimes disappears on a whim
for one or two days, right?
Hey, Raizo! There's a gate
to Kuri in the south!
What?!
Crap! I swore I'd die for him, and now
I'm late to join him on the battlefield!
This was a place filled with the stench
of death, blood, and violence!
It was like a different world.
All of their bloodlust was directed toward me!
I'll lop off your head, Kozuki Oden!
You're Kozuki Oden, huh?
I have been disowned,
so I no longer have a name!
You can enter all you like,
but we kill any who try to leave!
Especially samurai!
It is so restrictive!
How can anyone live in a place like this?!
That's hilarious.
You're never going to leave this place!
No, don't even try to leave!
"Don't even try to leave"?
That is my least favorite rule!
I make the rules here!
Cut him down!
That makes you the boss?
– Oden!
Oden!
Look! The gate has been broken!
How can an ass who grew up
pampered in the capital...
understand what it's like to live in hell?!
Is that all you really want to say?!
Look!
Up there!
Oden! We're here to back you up!
I must apologize.
I seem to have finished up already.
It took me an entire day and night.
Kill me already!
I know what the future holds anyway.
I've got nothing to live for!
This is the infamous Ashura Doji?!
Hey, you guys!
Do you still love me?
Lend me your wisdom and strength!
I have decided that the worthless scum here...
need me as their king!
My lord, Shogun! Lord Oden is at it again!
What? What did he do this time?!
Look at this!
That lawless Kuri...
Only he could do this...
Is this all true?
Leading the roughnecks
of the bloody and hellish land of Kuri,
Oden utilized their abundant energy
to turn the wild land into a habitable place.
After hearing of this accomplishment,
Shogun Kozuki Sukiyaki revoked his disownment
and bestowed upon his son
the title of daimyo of Kuri.
Our great Lord Oden will become
the daimyo of Kuri!
Hooray!
Then it'll become a full-fledged province!
I can't believe it! But we
stuck it out to the end!
Kin...
You did it! Our beloved Oden did it!
Hooray!
You're amazing, Oden!
You're finally Kuri's–
Oden!
Absolutely!
Daimyo!
– Lord Oden!
What is the matter, Ashura?
I...
have never seen peace before.
Thank you, Oden!
Stop it! You are creeping me out!
You bastard!
What're you doing?! Stop it!
Hey!
I said "Stop it"!
Screw you!
Knock it off already!
Now, a daimyo requires retainers.
Instead of surrounding myself
with the usual wise and sober men...
I would rather have you all.
Be my samurai!
– Lord Oden!
S-S-Stop it!
Your snot! Your snot!
It is dripping! Oh, it is on me!
Stop it!
Six years after that moment in time...
yet thirty-three years before the present day...
across the world, disbanded members
of the legendary Rocks Pirates
each formed a new crew, extended
their influence, and became infamous.
What are they? Animals?
Hairy humans?
Deformed monsters?
Did you get it?
Yeah...
In the distant past, many centuries ago,
we minks and the samurai
of Wano's Kozuki Clan
made a pledge to become sworn brothers.
Damn! Wano is the worst!
Dammit! Let me down!
I'm a kappa!
Which makes you a monster!
I wish we'd never set sail!
I wish we hadn't come here!
This isn't how you treat brothers!
A cat monster, dog monster, and a kappa...
Is this beach cursed?
Let's burn them alive!
Don't do it!
That is plenty of ingredients for today's oden...
You wretches!
You should all be ashamed!
You fear what is different out of ignorance!
It is pathetic to torment such little creatures!
Thank you...
Farewell.
– Don't leave us like this!
So, who are the monsters?
They followed me.
Thank you for saving us!
It's hot!
Between starvation, a shipwreck,
and a violent mob, we almost died!
Ouch!
Hey! This is too hot to eat!
Whoa...
I still can't get used to seeing animals talking.
The minks!
My father once told me about them.
I thought so!
We have that symbol in our country, too!
You-gara and our people are brothers!
And you saved our lives!
We were starving...
I see...
Eat as much as you want.
Here's to our savior.
Ouch!
Don't be shy.
You'll like the radish.
I won't forget this favor.
Hot!
Try the hanpen.
Ouch!
The konnyaku–
No! It's too hot to eat!
My tongue is sensitive like a cat's!
Bad cat!
Hey! Wait, Cat!
Hey, Cat!
Oden was meant...
to boil!
– That's kinda cool!
Tastes good to me.
And what are you?!
The ship my mother and I were on sank, and...
we were cast ashore in this country.
We asked for help, but people threw
rocks at us for being fishmen.
My mother got hurt, so we couldn't
go back to where we came from.
Before my mother died, she told me,
"Fishmen suffer discrimination...
so claim that you're a kappa."
I'm Kawamatsu the Kappa.
I've been living off leftovers.
Thank you for saving me
and treating me to such a delicious meal.
I'll never forget this.
May I eat the rest?
Nonesense. We'll cook more,
so just wait a bit.
No, that's not necessary. It's still edible.
Oh no...
I failed to express proper gratitude.
I wasted food.
You've grown up.
I'm meowwy sorry, Kappa!
I'll eat it, too!
It's still too hot!
What an amusing cat!
Cat!
There must still be creatures
out there I've never seen before.
Meeting you all has reinvigorated
my desire to one day set sail!
Sounds great!
The world's a big place!
Well then, take care!
Let us stay here!
Were you listening to us?!
We have no place to go!
All right! All right!
Yay!
We got more people...
I guess you just can't reject anyone.
That's fine and all, but we're in a bind here.
You lent money to Orochi
without asking me again!
Why would you help that creep?!
You see...
He may be independent now, but with
his ties to Yasuie, I cannot abandon him.
Silent steps. Stealthy steps. Ninja steps.
Understood? These are the fundamentals.
– Okay!
Let's go!
Don't be afraid of Yasuie!
Silent steps. Stealthy steps. Ninja steps.
– Silent steps. Stealthy steps. Ninja steps.
Why would you want to
steal this much money?
Lord Oden was broke!
If you're gonna kill us,
just do it already, you hedgehog!
If it'll help Lord Oden...
I'm happy to die!
Damn you, Oden. You certainly
know how to pick them.
I am giving you the money
you tried to steal.
– What?!
Lord Yasuie! These are Hakumai's funds!
And...?
You can have this too. It is yours!
Even more money?!
You gotta be kidding me! Is this a trap?!
Do you love Oden?
Then take this money, make yourselves presentable,
learn some manners, buy some books, and study!
These don't suit us!
I am...
No! Speak from your stomach!
I am...!
Having a bunch of lowlife retainers
like you would only disgrace Oden!
Lord Oden, would you kindly elaborate
on your temperament this fine morning?
This ganmodoki is exquisite!
What is the matter with you all?!
You are all creeping me out!
He is the man who will one day
become the shogun of Wano!
Those who serve him ought to be
the best samurai Wano has to offer!
Of course, protecting your lord is a must.
The capital city...
No, the entire country of Wano
will have you as its guardians!
I hear the daimyo of Kuri
and his court are coming to the capital.
Make sure you don't get robbed.
Lord Oden's retainers are known thugs.
Look! They're here!
– Wha...?
– Huh?
What?!
Oh, my! Look at those samurai!
Were Lord Oden's retainers
always so dignified?
I hardly recognized them!
It's like a shogun's procession!
The regal postures of those samurai were
so glorious that some people even forgot to breathe.
And one could have seen people drop
to their knees everywhere in the capital.
Hey, Father!
Oden!
You have become such a fine man!
Everyone is surprised!
I have only been made into a fine man.
But I am still the same as ever!
M-M-My Oden feels grateful toward others?!
Why should that scare you?
Hearing of his father's illness, Oden rushed to the capital
and was relieved to see him in good health.
However, this would be the last time
they ever exchanged words.
It seems this place is inhabited.
Pops, it'll take a week to repair it.
The water damaged most of the cargo!
We need to procure supplies.
Who wants to go?!
Almost everyone since we all
need some exercise.
We climbed up the falls, right?
Why is there sea and an island here?
We have a problem, Sir Kanjuro!
What is it?
Calm yourself! You are too loud!
We received a report that
a pirate ship docked at Itachi Port!
Pirates?!
Lord Oden!
Where are you going?!
To the port!
Here I go! Here I go!
Alright, we'll go fetch some supplies.
I'm coming, too!
You can't.
You're just an apprentice!
Don't say that!
Pops! Can I go?
Do as you like.
All right! Let's go!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I said no apprentices allowed!
Stay here!
What?!
Lord Oden went to the port?!
Why did you let him go?!
I heard there's a pirate ship at Itachi Port!
It's unusual, too!
They say it's big and the pirates look tough!
We must stop him!
He just went to chase them away, right?!
Not likely!
I am sure you know about...
Lord Oden's dream!
Is that a pirate ship?!
I have been waiting...
for this moment!
Here comes trouble.
Hey, all of you! Stand back!
– What?
Something's coming!
Something unthinkable!
Well done!
You made it past the terrible weather
and waterfalls! Quite impressive!
I have been waiting for you, pirates!
You are really something else!
I'll make you pay for that!
Bring it on, you punk!
I have been waiting for someone like you!
My name is Kozuki Oden!
I do not know who you are,
but please allow me...
to ride on your ship!